please take care of me
Good afternoon.
Hello.
We're starting, so say hello to this one, too.
Hello, everybody.
Hello. - Hello.
We're XYZ.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, so...
I'm home.
Where are we?
Where are you?
In the kitchen.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, the kitchen.
We are in the Kitchen Studio.
We're releasing our second EP, Sweet & Sour, on July 31st.
We're going to release our second EP, Sweet & Sour, on July 31st, and as part of the campaign, we're going to put a video for our fans.
We did a social networking campaign.
We're going to draw lots of people who post a video of their favorite Sweet & Sour song.
We drew 5 winners.
So five people came.
Wow, that's a terrible explanation.
Why not?
Well, we're releasing a new EPS Sweet & Sour on July 31st.
We're releasing a new EPS, Sweet & Sour.
So I wanted to use the song "Sweet & Sour
I wanted to give something back to the people who posted it on social media.
I've chosen them in a drawing.
I'm giving away 5 copies of
You know what?
to come and give something back.
Thank you.
This way.
And today we're going to
I'm going to treat you to homemade pancakes.
We're going to serve them.
Are you happy?
It's called
A sweet moment in front of me.
Do you guys make a lot of pancakes?
Yeah, I do.
No kidding?
You know, when I was a kid, I was a mom, and I made pancakes.
I'm here, come on. It's not a song.
I used to make them a lot, but I don't make them now because of the current situation.
I know, right? It's been a long time, hasn't it?
I made one a long time ago.
I bought one of those thicker ones four years ago, and used it only once.
I used to do that when I was doing something called "Oba-activism".
On Twitter.
I would make pancakes just for that.
Just for the leaves.
People do more than that.
I made pancakes for friends who came over and wanted some.
A little bit.
But it's been a while.
Like this year?
Yes, it's been a while.
So today, I have a lot of ingredients.
So today, I have a lot of ingredients, so I'd like to make it freely.
There are people who bake, people who mix, and people who cook.
I'm also planning to make fruit juice today.
I'd like to split up into two groups, one for baking and the other for mixing the fruit juice.
We're going to divide into two groups.
What are you going to introduce?
That?
You're going to make that?
Yes.
Let's go in order. You want to jupe like this?
You see these flaats here? These are the pancakes and the juices.
There's avocado, there's vegetables, right?
And there's coconut milk, which we probably used for juice, and canned fruit, and chocolate pens, and...
And there are also chocolate pens, yes.
The pancake batter that we have prepared for you does not require any whisking.
No whisking.
It's easy.
I had them prepare it for us.
Made in Japan.
Two kinds?
This one is gluten-free.
Nikina loves it.
In the fridge
Highballs.
Highball and milk.
Milk
melon
Kiwi
Fresh cream
Butter and margarine
There is ice cream and fruit in the freezer.
There is also ice cream and fruit in the freezer!
Yay, ice cream!
Let's make something with it!
I want to make some kind of bean jam butter!
I'm going to make an-butter today!
I was just talking about that.
The two in the middle, hold out your hands.
Put your hands in the air, like this.
Not with a "goo", but a "par".
Not goo. Pow.
I told you we're cooking today, didn't I?
I did!
What are those fingernails?
Mothers.
They're not mothers.
You changed them yesterday, didn't you, Yuki?
Yes!
I changed it yesterday.
For today?
Yes.
So we'll just...
Mix it up.
Or bake it.
We don't cut.
With Yuko
And the soup?
What are you going to do with it?
Fresh juice.
I'm going to pick it up. And I'm going to wash my hands.
Mikina, like this.
I know, I know. She washes her hands more than anyone else.
That's right, Mikina, you wash your hands more than anyone else.
Let's go next.
Ai-chan, like this.
No, no, no.
I don't like it.
I hate it when you do that.
It's too early.
Let's cook!
Dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan!
Pang, pang, pang, pang
Pan-pan-pan
pang pang pang
pampan
No lightweight cup
Please use rice portions
Oh no!
Oh, you're good at Yuki.
That's 5 grams.
You get the idea.
You can tell by how sticky it is.
This is for now.
One for toppings, one for juice.
Okay, this one.
But this one?
This one's good for juice.
That's three slices.
Where are they?
Oh, I've already got one.
All right, everyone.
We've got a lot of questions on the hashtag, so please answer them while you cook.
Okay. I'd love to hear your questions, so please think about them.
So please think about it.
It's funny how quiet everyone is.
That's right.
Can I ask a question? Go ahead.
Uchi.
If you were to recommend a song, including the songs on this EP, to someone who doesn't know X-WISE, which song would you choose?
I'd like to hear from you because I have many opportunities to do so.
Do you mean you would include songs not on the EP?
Yes, if I were to recommend a song to someone who doesn't know X-WISE, including this EP, which song would I recommend?
If you were to recommend a song from X-WISE to someone who doesn't know it, what would you recommend? I mean, what would you recommend to people who don't know X-WISE?
If I had to pick one from the EP, I'd say...
Practice in the elliptical
Drama and
Drama is
It's really just like the name
because it was in the theme song of a one-man drama
It's in whatever video
It's playing, you know, usually
It's in the opening or the ending
Drama ending.
Do they do a string scene or something?
Yeah.
What about Nakonya?
Let's see...
I'm...
A little bit.
Blake.
Wrong, EP.
I wasn't wrong.
I was just shaking my face in pieces and I forgot everything I said.
Mao-chan did the EP.
She picked it out of the EP.
I think the EP is a crystal sour.
I know, right?
Well, okay.
Okay.
So you're gonna tell me what it is?
EP's Colorful
Presents.
Oh.
Oh, you got a present for me.
I love it. I love it.
Yeah, I love the present.
Have fun with this guy.
What about you?
She was a sater and sour, too.
Oh, yeah, we're the same.
I'm just curious.
You know what? Let me jangle.
I had to put the pancake mix in after the eggs and milk.
I opened it first.
I was a little too hepatic.
I'm sorry.
Get better.
Okay, next question!
Mikuchin
Who eats the most among the members?
Yuki-chan.
But I don't know... lately...
Yuki and Now.
Do you have an episode of how much you ate?
Well, when I went to an all-you-can-eat Jinggistan in Hokkaido...
Was it the most average?
If it was the most average...
That's scary.
Hey, you guys...
Did I eat the first portion?
Yes, I did.
Your stomach was so full.
Seriously, Yuki-chan, you were amazing today.
She ate so much she had a baby inside.
That's for sure.
She ate 4 onigiri today.
And about 3 hot snacks.
Then she decided to eat this today.
I'll get the knife.
It's okay.
It's fine...
I guess.
But...
I eat when I drink.
My stomach is limitless.
That's why the next day, I had a body at Matsuya's that I didn't recognize.
Was he a caketcher?
No, I don't eat.
I'd eat, and then I'd come home in the morning, after I was done.
The body of Matsuya...
He's a caketcha type.
And the next thing I know, I'm in the house.
Then I'll let all of you answer
Nishimura-san
What is your favorite onigiri ingredient?
Dried shrimp
Tsumamayo
Beef shigure
Onigiri
Find your favorite onigiri shop.
It's about 150 yen.
The onigiri shop there is more expensive.
It costs about 350 yen.
That's true. Kinna-chan always does.
That's right.
Delicious!
Even if I'm running late, I'll just lie and go drink.
That has nothing to do with being late.
He buys them in time for transfers.
Really?
It doesn't matter.
It's done.
It's done?
Bake it right now.
The dough is ready.
That's the first one.
Good night.
I'm going to bake it.
Don't let it sit too long or it won't puff up.
I see.
Then we'll bake it over here.
I'm gonna bake it.
I'm going to bake it.
What are you gonna bake?
It's okay.
I'll do it for you, Kansaki-chan.
It'll be fine.
Did you butter it?
You didn't butter it?
What? Santambar.
But it tastes better with butter.
Okay, then. Butterloo.
We have margarine, too.
I'll go ask him a question.
Natsuhi.
Please tell us what is your favorite dish.
Yes, by all means, please answer!
Stewed rice
Stewed hamburger steak
Omusami
Is it that cute?
Hayashi Rice
But you can make anything, can't you?
I can make simmered dishes too.
Sure.
What's that?
Didn't you make rice with gapao?
No, that's not it. That's my sister's.
Is that Doli?
Doli?
I'm impressed you can make anything.
Miso soup.
I know.
Miso soup is the most amazing thing I've ever made.
What, you just add dried ingredients?
What?
What about our miso soup?
By the way, have you ever had a home-cooked meal from any of the members?
Yuki's?
Yuki brought Maho-chan some kiriboshi-daikon (dried daikon radish), which is similar to chikuzen.
Maho and a drink
Butter!
I can't eat it!
It's dangerous!
You dropped the butter.
All of it?
I'm sorry, 10 grams.
Put it down and I'll cut it for you.
It's out of butter.
But I wish you'd cut me some more.
It's all apples.
Thank you.
What do you mean?
I thought they were pears.
They're still apples even when they're long.
But that's okay, there's plenty to go around.
Heat a frying pan over medium heat.
Oh, no.
Something's different.
It smells like sand.
Once the pan is hot, take it off the heat
Put it on a damp cloth.
You want to get a rag?
Come on, come on, come on.
What's a wet cloth?
A wet cloth. You put it on the pan.
I don't have a rag!
Okay, I'll go next time.
Ena-san, what X-TWICE songs are fun to dance and sing to?
Fun songs?
Yes, I do.
It's the one with the beautiful grill marks.
What did you say?
Exercise songs, fun songs to sing and dance to.
Metronosi.
You know what I mean?
Un nonsense.
Okay, go.
Naw?
What is it?
You can sing.
Nau...
It's fun to sing a lot, but it's fun to sing Higher.
I'm not laughing.
Hey, hey, it's not round at all
It's like an obourez.
No, it's not.
It's okay, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute.
I see it.
It's cute.
I don't know.
Why don't you try one?
It's really viscous.
Yeah, right.
Did you use milk?
I don't know, let's try one.
Is that a kiwi you're peeling clean?
Because...
You can peel them?
Yes, I can!
You're both so good
Mako...
Benky!
Tibby.
Okay, so if any of you have any questions, please raise your hand.
Please raise your hand.
Oh, Katie.
I picked and chose what you all are wearing today? I'd like to ask you a question about...
Why did you choose this apron?
The reason for the apron?
Then please tell me your point.
I chose a color of apron that I don't usually have.
I don't usually have an apron.
I have one.
Yes, you do.
That's great.
That's how you choose.
I chose an apron in a color I don't have.
Is it pretty?
It's cute.
Today, Yuki-chan...
Your makeup is a little different to match the apron.
Your makeup is a little different.
Yes, I'm wearing a lighter makeup today.
The newlywed makeup.
Natural.
I'm happy to do it.
Thank you.
I bought it at Francfranc.
I made a mistake.
You know what?
The ribbon is big, and the polka dots are cute.
You do that in front of the ribbon?
Do it.
When was that?
Great help, Yuusha!
Let everyone show you who they are.
His conch yi
A normal
We are a town
Souzuki chan's ka decline.
pirate land
Kakko pratic.
I bought this painting because I thought it would look good on me.
I'd be embarrassed if I slept in the bath with Maho
The colors are the same.
But it looks good on me, right?
Right? It looks good on you.
Yes, it does.
You had the bag, Mikina.
Yes, I did.
Yuki, I wanted you to prepare Mikina.
Really?
Yeah.
You know, Yuki's apron, too.
I liked that.
Yes.
But I thought Mikina would definitely wear it.
Then another one went.
Yes.
Then I went to do it again.
By the way, I bought it with Universal's receipt.
But there's one person who spent over 5,000 yen.
That would be me, Fran-Fran.
It's me, Fran-Fran.
I rented it out.
Anyway...
The decorations, they're so pretty.
I had to rent it out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't have a lid. I'm putting a lid on it.
I'm sorry, sir. There's no lid.
There's no lid?
It says to put the lid on, but we don't have a lid.
Why don't you use this?
We need more lids.
What?
It's better than no lid.
Let's go for it.
I want to make it.
So, I'm gonna put the lid on like this.
Here's the pitcher.
I'll either eat sweet candy for the rest of my life, or I'll eat candy for the rest of my life.
Either I'll eat sweet candy for the rest of my life, or I'll eat salty candy for the rest of my life.
Uh...
Maybe a little bit salty.
What?
It's too salty.
Because, you know, sweet ones are too sweet.
Too much potato. Too much potato. Too much salt.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's a big world out there.
Oh, my God, it's sweet.
Why?
Too much salt makes my face swell up.
It's not like he only eats sweets.
I eat a lot of sweets. I'll eat all my meals with them.
I like sweets, so I'll make it sweet.
I like sweets. I like sweets too.
I can't eat a lot of sweets these days.
I can't eat them.
I get too focused when I don't have time to talk.
It's pink. Which one is it?
The salty one's the same.
So you're the only one left out.
You're the only one left out.
Poor girl.
I can live on my own.
You're right. You're strong.
I don't mind.
I'm done, doctor.
Thank you.
That's wonderful.
I've got something.
Okay, then.
Melon?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no.
Some kind of omelet.
Looks good. Omelette-omelette.
The heat's too weak. Can't you fry it?
Fry it. No, there's no lid.
You can fry it without the lid, but it's like...
But you know what I mean. It's like it's raw.
Kanko, cut the melon?
I want some melon. You want some melon?
Then we'll cut it now. It's burning.
But I'll cut it.
So I'll do the dishes.
Oh, no, no, no...
This is Clear Shin-chan's face.
Wrong again.
Oh, no!
Learn it!
I can't see this.
This is tricky.
But it's all right... if you mix it.
Oh, that's good, that's good.
It's gonna be raw.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Keep mixing it.
Do you have a toothpick for this?
We'll never know if we don't mix it.
It's coming in milk.
Are you okay? I'll take care of it.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Is it mixed in?
It's like two rocks.
I don't think we should give them away.
We'll eat it.
Maho and Mikiya, what do you think you're doing?
We just finished cutting them.
We cut the best melon tea.
Nice melon.
It's rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Okay, any more questions?
Yes, sir.
What is the difference between pancakes and pancakes?
Pancakes and pancakes?
May I? Excuse me, Mikina.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to scare you.
The difference between pancakes and pancakes?
I wonder.
Do you go out in a fancy restaurant or an old-fashioned one?
Or fluffy.
There you go. There you go.
Fluffy or hard?
Or hard?
Pancakes are more expensive.
What do you think?
Do you have any fruit on hand?
Yes, they do.
Pancakes don't often have fruit, do they?
Hey, look, Kira, look.
You can do it!
Here's the answer.
Answers? You still have answers for me?
Do you have the right answer?
I checked.
Oh, you got it right.
In Japan, pancakes and hot cakes are often thought of as the same thing.
But the name "pancake" originated in Japan.
Therefore, it is not understood when calling them pancakes in other countries.
That's for sure.
You mean Japanese-English?
Because both are made using a frying pan or a saucepan
In a larger sense, pancakes are the same as pancakes.
However, the difference is that pancakes are sweet, while pancakes are not sweet, and some meals are not sweet.
that is what is meant by "sweet" and "savory".
You're right.
Can't you get rid of it?
Shazy chin?
Isn't it too funny?
Pancakes don't go that fast.
It's not the lid.
It's not the lid? Oh, my God.
Well, maybe there is one, if we look for it.
They're kind of small, all of them.
It's on the pot.
It's a small one.
This is the best one.
It's burnt.
Maybe it's not working at all? This one.
Oh, my God.
I got it this way.
That's good.
It's good.
It's working.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, I'll look it up on my phone.
How do you know which juice is the best?
I've always had my own Classil.
It's the kind with sugar in it, isn't it?
You're the kind of guy who puts sugar in it?
I'd like to make the first juice.
I'd like to make my first juice.
Applause.
Please, please.
What are you going to put in it?
I'll just make a little first.
I'll make a little bit.
I'll start with bananas.
I'm pretty sure bananas.
Definitely bananas.
And I'll add frozen berries.
I'll put in frozen berries.
Bring them in.
I'm thinking melon.
Juice?
Melon is a luxury juice.
That's good.
I don't know if I want berries or melon.
Coconut.
Coconut? Coconut milk?
Is that what you put in it?
That's what you put in it.
Would you like to try it?
And milk.
Milk.
I think this is it.
Here.
I believe in the sweetness of the ingredients.
Oh, is a little bit too much?
Is it normal?
Just a little bit?
You don't put water in it?
No water.
Try one here at Tommy Blue.
One time. One time.
One time.
Just this one.
I don't know.
Just this once.
Here.
Isn't it enough?
It's done.
Here it is.
Looks bananas.
What's that? Is it good?
It smells good.
Looks good.
You can take a sip now.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's just fruit, but it's sweet?
Sweet. This is sweet.
Oh, yeah, because coconut milk is sweet.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Next.
I can go on and on and on, but this is just like...
Yeah, senior.
So...
Here we go.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Make as much as you can.
I'll make as much as I can and serve it.
Okay, okay! Berries, then.
Who likes berries?
I'll take orders.
Do you like berries?
I love berries.
We have melon right now.
Melons, kiwis, apples, berries.
Tell him what you like.
Melons.
Kiwi.
So you're going to put in the ones that everyone says they like?
That's right.
I don't think it's a good combination.
Let's just ask.
Okay, apple.
Oh, then berries.
What's that?
Banana, melon?
Oh, there's bananas, too.
Banana.
Apples.
Okay, then.
Yay.
Try it on the barbara.
Birrin, then.
I want Birrin on mine, too.
And, oh no.
what is it?
Try it on Bicua.
I feel like I'm doing something really sneaky on the right.
I think I've decided not to look at my right side anymore.
I've decided not to look to my right.
Hey, hey, do you like bananas?
I love bananas.
I like bananas too. I'll put them in there.
Oh, my God, you have a lot of bananas.
You love bananas.
It sounds like it's really hard.
I've stopped listening to the service.
I've stopped asking about the service.
I'll do whatever I want.
I'll do what I want.
Is that what pancakes are like?
Pancakes?
I do this all the time.
This is the best.
Pancakes.
Do you get the frying pan so dirty when you accept the pancakes?
Done!
It's done!
You're good!
You did it!
A plate!
Here it is!
Finally, the master's pancakes are done!
Now, let's get the plate!
Yes!
Like a plate.
What are you doing with this?
Here we go!
Looks good!
Wow!
Oh, yeah!
There's hot water in it!
Oh!
What if I do this?
What did you mix?
Berry mix, banana and soy milk.
It's so good!
Why don't you put sugar in it now?
Let's put sugar in it.
Branulated sugar.
Got it! Thank you.
I've got all these questions, and I haven't answered any of them.
Let's answer a lot of them!
Taro-chan.
What is your favorite X-WISE outfit?
One at a time, please.
Budokan
Can I go to Budokan one time? Yukimo
Iration Tour
Say for Eyes
Please wait
Iration part 2 would be nice
Iration Tour
Maybe jacket part 2.
Budokan would be nice.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. About 10,000 more yen.
Next question
Mr. Isatin
If you were a master, who would you have known?
Maho
What?
That's the first time I've heard that.
Aha.
That's very difficult.
I think it changes with the seasons.
That's right.
It depends on the season.
I think it depends on the season.
I guess I'm a box person, right?
It's hard.
Courage?
Courage is courage.
Why? What's your favorite part?
She's cute.
She's kind.
Bright
Bright.
I'm sure of it.
That's the most important thing.
You Germans are amazing.
Yuki, you tend to like mood makers.
You tend to like people who are mood makers.
You're aware of being the mood maker of the group?
Yes, I am.
Without me, this group would be eaten up. Thank you.
Yes, this is
Mayu.
Here you go.
Why?
Hmm?
Mai-chan?
I don't know.
I like girls who smile a lot.
I like girls who laugh a lot.
Hmm...
And usually...
Normal.
I usually like them.
Okay, next question.
I'll let Maho answer this one.
Let's see...
Mr. Cabbage, what is the worst thing you've done this year?
What have you done the most this year?
I've done a lot of things.
Lots of things.
Forgot my bullet train ticket.
Headband.
Where?
You forgot your zoo ticket. You forgot your ramen shop ticket.
I forgot the key to the recording studio.
House key?
Did I know that? - No.
No, in the cab.
You forgot your wallet.
I left my wallet and my house key and everything in the cab when I came to pitch, and I forgot everything.
Cab?
Oh, there it is. That's it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Nice.
Okay, Mami.
Mami!
Face the camera.
One by one.
I want to see them all.
Here?
Face this camera, one at a time.
Here we go.
Don't miss it.
Mami.
She doesn't like it.
It's just for today.
But it's going to be on TV?
What's wrong?
Did you put water in?
I need to put some water in.
That's funny.
You don't want to miss out on too much, do you?
What if I do?
Tell me.
Don't miss it!
He's cute.
So cute!
Yuki did her best.
He's so cute!
Here it comes. Here it comes.
I'm scared.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shouldn't it take this long?
It's ice-cold, that's for sure.
My eyes are all dried out.
Wait a minute.
I don't know, but I'm decorating.
I've got three more to go, then I'm done decorating.
But we haven't eaten yet.
I'm sure you're right.
I don't know.
It's fine.
It's so messy.
It's got chocolate in it.
But it's hard to do, isn't it?
I'm going to put nine-tenths in.
Don't put it back in.
Like this.
Again. Again.
One more time.
Did we record it?
I don't remember at all.
Oh, right. Now it's time to not miss it.
Mikino-chan, do you change it up a little bit for each show?
Yes, I think so.
Depends on the triangle.
I'm in the mood.
I have a mood.
I haven't done it yet.
You haven't done it yet?
Oh, I was asleep.
People don't do it when they're worried you'll hear them.
I'm sure you're right about that.
It was agonizingly painful.
You're good.
You want to try this?
Let's use curtains.
You've already done it so well, Yuki-chan.
You have to try.
A dozen times already.
What did you do?
Pushing the mixer.
Push the mixer.
I'm pretty sure she can't hear you, so you might want to hold it down ten more times.
Can I push it again?
You know what, I think I'm ready for the decorations now.
Thank you very much.
It's for ampersanders. When it's all buttered up.
Okay, Mr. Kobayashi, is that it?
Are you ready to serve?
I'm ready to serve.
I'll serve it.
Yes, please.
What a great kid you have here.
Isn't it good?
I could make the juice with my own eyes.
That's good.
I'll get you all some ice cream later.
Zoo pancakes!
They're so good!
This is so good!
Kiwi people are sour!
It's done! It's done!
Thank you, Mikuchi!
You're the best at asking about yourself.
Amazing!
He's asking about the one on the left.
He's a spreader.
He's cute.
Bananas?
Let me get this weeping burr.
It's time to go.
Shake hands.
My hand
Wings...
hands and wings are scattered
ideal difference
儿子
difficult to Japanese language痴人
Mecha manga audience banquet
Tokyo Denpa
While doing it with a tentative video
The video is in Kansai, but it's a plate.
I don't care what you do with it.
Riku Kiku sollte
Mekigachamakiseke.
What?
Charlotte&.
Elise upfront
Rock, paper, scissors.
Come on, let's eat.
Yes, ma'am.
You look nice.
I'll do it.
All right.
Cake.
Oh, my God.
It's iced cake.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
It's a cake.
Where are you going to put it?
Oh, my God.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's okay.
You're not too bad, right? - I'm good to go... ah ah ah ah ah... it's like I'm in this.
This is what I'm here for!
It's gone!
Okay, everyone, let's eat!
Get up!
Stom! Excuse me!
Me.
Shouldn't we put it down?
You should put it down.
We have whipped cream.
Do you think so? I don't know?
I don't know. I don't know. What do you think?
Where do we start?
Ah!
Here you go.
Chef's pancakes.
Are they good?
Thanks for making the pancakes.
Thank you very much.
It's a taste of Maken.
I knew the pancake meal would disappear.
It's going away.
Good luck with that.
Yes, sir! So...
Pancake making is finished!
We did it!
How was it? Try it.
It took longer than I thought it would.
I knew it would be for five people.
plus four of ours, I was pretty much a part-time leader.
That's true.
That's true. There were times when there was no work to be done.
Despite all the happenings, I am glad to hear that we were able to make a delicious meal.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was only for a moment.
It was a moment.
On the contrary, it took a while to make it.
It took a while.
I'm glad we were able to make something good.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
Yes, I mean that.
And Sweet & Sour.
Listen up.
I hope you're watching the pancakes with me and I hope you're eating them too.
Thank you so much for all the other submissions!
So, as for our future plans...
We've decided to add an additional show to our Futural Free Tour!
September 8 at ZEPP Shinjuku
And on September 28th and 29th, we will have an additional show in Okinawa.
We hope to have a great time with everyone who comes to see us!
We are looking forward to seeing you!
And on August 17, we will be performing at Station!
Yay!
It means the evening is coming.
We have a lot of songs we want to sing with you.
We are looking forward to seeing you all at the station and hope that you will come and enjoy the summer with us.
We are looking forward to seeing you soon!
That's all for us XYZ... See you soon!